#### Contact

9304154450 (Mobile) ak858098@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/aayush-kumar-65993a235 (LinkedIn)

#### Top Skills

RESTful WebServices
Data Structures
Scripting

# Aayush Kumar

Full Stack Engineer @ Nexxio | MERN Specialist | AWS Cloud | Docker & Kubernetes Architect | Al developer

Bengaluru, Karnataka, India

# Summary

As a Full Stack Engineer, I develop, maintain and scale web applications using the MERN stack, AWS, Docker and Kubernetes, while integrating AI technologies for enhanced functionality. I leverage machine learning models to create intelligent features and personalized experiences. My core competencies include analytical thinking, creativity, teamwork, and communication across both traditional development and AI domains.

# Experience

Nexxio

Full Stack Engineer May 2024 - Present (1 year 1 month)

Bengaluru, Karnataka, India

City Link Portal Pvt Ltd, Bangalore, India Software Engineer September 2022 - May 2024 (1 year 9 months) Bengaluru, Karnataka, India

Chegg India
Subject Matter Expert
March 2021 - May 2023 (2 years 3 months)
India

FunctionUp
Trainee
March 2022 - August 2022 (6 months)
India

### Education

Swami Vivekanand Institute of Engineering & Technology, Banur Page 1 of 2 Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Mechanical Engineering · (2017 - 2021)

## DAV Kapil Dev Public School

Intermediate, Science and Maths · (March 2015 - May 2017)